<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>April 8 update 1</title>
<link>example.com/</link>
<description>lm  tester</description>
<!--   -->
<!-- 0 -->
<item>
<title>Header-CTO-Katusa-American Lithium 3</title>
<link>example.com/1</link>
<guid>example.com/1</guid>
<description>placeholder</description>
</item>
<!-- https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/snippet.xml -->
<!-- 1 -->
<item>
<title>Placeholde2r</title>
<link>example.com/2</link>
<guid>example.com/2</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 1999 12:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
<description>placeholder</description>
</item>
<!--  -->
<!-- 2 -->
<!-- Inbox News RSS snippets -->
<item>
<snipOpen>{{{snippet</snipOpen>
<snipClose>}}}</snipClose>
<INsnip>testSNIPPET</INsnip>
<INid></INid>
<SMHsnip></SMHsnip>
<SMHid></SMHid>
<SMHsnipTwo></SMHsnipTwo>
<SMHidTwo></SMHidTwo>
<MBsnip></MBsnip>
<MBid></MBid>
<LCsnip></LCsnip>
<LCid></LCid>
<DRsnip></DRsnip>
<DRid></DRid>
<TLIsnip></TLIsnip>
<TLIid></TLIid>
</item>
  <!-- 4:30 7 at 7 / TLI update --> 
<!-- Editorial Schedule 7, 8, 9, 12 || 4, 4:30, 7, 8 --> 
<!-- 3 -->
<!-- Daily Recap EdMention snippets -->
  <!-- 8pm -->
<item>
<DRheader>Snippy 1</DRheader>
<DRhID>snippy 2</DRhID>
<DRheaderII></DRheaderII>
<DRhIDii></DRhIDii>
<DRspaceAd>snippy 3</DRspaceAd>
<DRsID>snippy 4</DRsID>
<DRspaceAdII>snippy 5</DRspaceAdII>
<DRsIDii>snippy 6</DRsIDii>
  <DRspaceAdIII>snippy 7</DRspaceAdIII>
<DRsIDiii>snippy 8</DRsIDiii>
</item>
  <!--  -->
<!-- 4 -->
  <!-- Autoblog snippets -->
  <!-- AIWU populates from SH and MB -->
  <!-- DTO and WTF populates from SH -->
<item>
<LMID>LM1544</LMID>
<snipOpen>{{{ snippet</snipOpen>
<snipClose>}}}</snipClose>
<SHDynamicSnip>Snippy 1</SHDynamicSnip>
<SHID>snippy 2</SHID>
<iDDynamicSnip>Snippy 1</iDDynamicSnip>
<iDID>snippy 2</iDID>
<OODynamicSnip>Snippy 1</OODynamicSnip>
<OOID>snippy 2</OOID>
<oneTwoThreeDynamicSnip>Snippy 1</oneTwoThreeDynamicSnip>
<ONEID>snippy 2</ONEID>
<SFMDynamicSnip>Snippy 1</SFMDynamicSnip>
<SFMID>snippy 2</SFMID>
<webinard>Tuesday March 22nd</webinard>
</item>
    <!--  -->
<!-- 5 -->
  <!-- Traffic Grid snippet -->
  <!--  -->
   <item>
    <aceSnipTwo>SIR FedQ - 41 Banks</aceSnipTwo>
  <aceIDtwo></aceIDtwo>
    <aceSnip>TMI-SF LASER 20</aceSnip>
  <aceID></aceID>
   <!--  -->
    <bmhSnip>BTM-wargames-spad492</bmhSnip>
  <bmhID></bmhID>
    <bmhSnipTwo>NP-lgr-cbdc-spad17</bmhSnipTwo>
  <bmhIDtwo></bmhIDtwo>
  </item>
  <!-- 6 -->
<!-- Morning Bullets EdMention snippets -->
  <!-- 9am and 4pm -->
<item>
<MBheader>Snippy 1</MBheader>
<MBhID>snippy 2</MBhID>
<MBspaceAd>snippy 3</MBspaceAd>
<MBsID>snippy 4</MBsID>
<MBspaceAdII>snippy 5</MBspaceAdII>
<MBsIDii>snippy 6</MBsIDii>
<MBspaceAdIII>snippy 7</MBspaceAdIII>
<MBsIDiii>snippy 8</MBsIDiii>
<!--  -->
<MBheaderPM>snippyy 1</MBheaderPM>
<MBhIDpm>snippyy 2</MBhIDpm>
<MBspaceAdpm>snippyy 3</MBspaceAdpm>
<MBsIDpm>snippyy 4</MBsIDpm>
<MBspaceAdIIpm>snippyy 5</MBspaceAdIIpm>
<MBsIDiipm>snippyy 6</MBsIDiipm>
</item>
  <!-- 7 -->
<!-- TLI EdMention snippets -->
  <!-- 8am -->
<item>
<TLIheader>Snippy 1</TLIheader>
<TLIhID>snippy 2</TLIhID>
<TLIheaderII></TLIheaderII>
<TLIhIDii></TLIhIDii>
<TLIspaceAd>snippy 3</TLIspaceAd>
<TLIsID>snippy 4</TLIsID>
<TLIspaceAdII>snippy 5</TLIspaceAdII>
<TLIsIDii>snippy 6</TLIsIDii>
  <TLIspaceAdIII>snippy 7</TLIspaceAdIII>
<TLIsIDiii>snippy 8</TLIsIDiii>
<!--  -->
<TLIheaderPM>snippyy 1</TLIheaderPM>
<TLIhIDpm>snippyy 2</TLIhIDpm>
<TLIspaceAdpm>snippyy 3</TLIspaceAdpm>
<TLIsIDpm>snippyy 4</TLIsIDpm>
<TLIspaceAdIIpm>snippyy 5</TLIspaceAdIIpm>
<TLIsIDiipm>snippyy 6</TLIsIDiipm>
</item>
  <!-- 8 -->
<!-- BU EdMention snippets -->
  <!-- 1030am and 4pm -->
  <!-- update all snippets at 10:30 -->
<item>
<BUheader>Snippy 1</BUheader>
<BUhID>snippy 2</BUhID>
<BUspaceAd>snippy 3</BUspaceAd>
<BUsID>snippy 4</BUsID>
<BUspaceAdII>snippy 5</BUspaceAdII>
<BUsIDii>snippy 6</BUsIDii>
<BUspaceAdIII>snippy 7</BUspaceAdIII>
<BUsIDiii>snippy 8</BUsIDiii>
<!--  -->
<BUheaderPM>snippyy 1</BUheaderPM>
<BUhIDpm>snippyy 2</BUhIDpm>
<BUspaceAdpm>snippyy 3</BUspaceAdpm>
<BUsIDpm>snippyy 4</BUsIDpm>
<BUspaceAdIIpm>snippyy 5</BUspaceAdIIpm>
<BUsIDiipm>snippyy 6</BUsIDiipm>
</item>
  <!-- 9 -->
<!-- LC EdMention snippets -->
  <!-- 0pm Main send, 11:30 5:30 - offshoot(PM) -->
<item>
<LCheader>Snippy 1</LCheader>
<LChID>snippy 2</LChID>
<LCspaceAd>snippy 3</LCspaceAd>
<LCsID>snippy 4</LCsID>
<LCspaceAdII>snippy 5</LCspaceAdII>
<LCsIDii>snippy 6</LCsIDii>
<LCspaceAdIII>snippy 7</LCspaceAdIII>
<LCsIDiii>snippy 8</LCsIDiii>
<!--  -->
<LCheaderPM>snippyy 1</LCheaderPM>
<LChIDpm>snippyy 2</LChIDpm>
<LCspaceAdpm>snippyy 3</LCspaceAdpm>
<LCsIDpm>snippyy 4</LCsIDpm>
<LCspaceAdIIpm>snippyy 5</LCspaceAdIIpm>
<LCsIDiipm>snippyy 6</LCsIDiipm>
</item>
  <!-- 10 -->
<!-- S7 -->
  <!-- 7am and 7pm -->
<item>
<SheaderAM>Snippy 1</SheaderAM>
<ShID>snippy 2</ShID>
<SspaceAd>snippy 3</SspaceAd>
<SsID>snippy 4</SsID>
<SspaceAdII>snippy 5</SspaceAdII>
<SsIDii>snippy 6</SsIDii>
  <SspaceAdIII>snippy 7</SspaceAdIII>
<SsIDiii>snippy 8</SsIDiii>
<!--  -->
  <SheaderPM>snippyy 1</SheaderPM>
<ShIDii>snippyy 2</ShIDii>
  <SspaceAdPM>snippyy 3</SspaceAdPM>
<SsIDpm>snippyy 4</SsIDpm>
<SspaceAdIIPM>snippyy 5</SspaceAdIIPM>
<SsIDiipm>snippyy 6</SsIDiipm>
</item>
  <!-- 11 -->
<!-- SMH EdMention snippets -->
<!-- 1pm -->
 
<item>
<SMHheader>Snippy 1</SMHheader>
<SMHhID>snippy 2</SMHhID>
<SMHspaceAd>snippy 3</SMHspaceAd>
<SMHsID>snippy 4</SMHsID>
<SMHspaceAdII>snippy 5</SMHspaceAdII>
<SMHsIDii>snippy 6</SMHsIDii>
<SMHspaceAdIII>snippy 7</SMHspaceAdIII>
<SMHhIDiii>snippy 8</SMHhIDiii>
</item>

    <!-- 12 -->
<!-- ACE INTRO -->
<!-- -->

<item>
<description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Another quarter, another surge in the markets. With the S&#038;P 500 and Nasdaq soaring over 10% for the second straight quarter, April's historical bullishness augurs well for continued momentum. Strength begets strength, signaling more upward trajectory ahead. While this bodes well for investors, there's even better news in store for us. Join me in today's Insight to uncover why this market surge spells opportunity.</description>
</item>

  <!-- 13 -->
<!-- Balanced Breif -->
<!-- -->

<item>
<intro>On this day in 1927, the first long-distance public television broadcast took place. Let's view today's news with the anticipation and wonder of those early television viewers.</intro>
<con>As we switch off today's broadcast, let's appreciate the vast advancements in communication and resolve to use these tools to build a more informed and connected world.</con>
<TBBone>Snippy 1</TBBone>
<TBBoneID>snippy 2</TBBoneID>
<TBBtwo>snippy 3</TBBtwo>
<TBBtwoID>snippy 4</TBBtwoID>
<TBBthree>snippy 5</TBBthree>
<TBBthreeID>snippy 6</TBBthreeID>
<TBBfour>snippy 7</TBBfour>
<TBBfourID>snippy 8</TBBfourID>
<TBBfive>Header-CPC-Beachside-Phyto Science-lm2825</TBBfive>
<TBBfiveID></TBBfiveID>
</item>

<!-- 14 -->
<!-- Weekend Intro/Outros -->
<!-- RSS Hybrid Test Template Weekend -->
<item>
    <!-- Ssev Section -->
    <SsevIntro>This serene Sunday, April 7, 20snippyy 4, we honor the birthday of the World Health Organization, established on this day in 1948. Its founding reflects a global commitment to ensuring the highest possible level of health for all people, reminding us of our shared responsibility towards each other's well-being.</SsevIntro>
    <SsevCon>"Health is a state of complete physical, mental and social well-being, and not merely the absence of disease or infirmity." —World Health Organization Constitution</SsevCon>
    <SsevStoryI>The Remarkable Rescue of 29 Fighting Dogs</SsevStoryI>
    <SsevMoreStoryI>In a heartwarming turn of events in Horry County, South Carolina, dozens of dogs once trapped in the brutal world of dog fighting have been given a chance to wag their tails again, thanks to the efforts of the Best Friends Animal Society and local animal welfare advocates. Rescued from cramped cages and the scars of their past, these adorable survivors are now embarking on a journey toward rehabilitation and eventual adoption, under the care of compassionate volunteers across the Southeast. With each dog exhibiting its own unique personality, from the lap-loving Willow to the shy but sweet Crawl, these pooches are learning to trust and love again. As these former fighters adjust to their new lives filled with affection and safety, the question arises: How can society better protect these innocent animals from being ensnared in such cruel circumstances again?</SsevMoreStoryI>
    <SsevImageI>https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/20snippyy 4/04/group-29-dogs-rescued-south-79490225.jpg</SsevImageI>
    <SsevLinkI>https://nypost.com/20snippyy 4/04/04/us-news/29-dogs-rescued-from-illegal-south-carolina-fighting-ring/</SsevLinkI>
    <SsevStoryII>Why Reba McEntire Is Laughing At Joy Behar</SsevStoryII>
    <SsevMoreStoryII>Amidst the buzz of Beyoncé's foray into country with "Cowboy Carter," Reba McEntire reacts with a blend of Southern charm and amusement to Joy Behar's critique of "Jolene" as anti-feminist. In a landscape where music and cultural commentary collide, McEntire's laughter offers a masterclass in grace, even as she welcomes Beyoncé's crossover with open arms. This juxtaposition of viewpoints, from Behar's feminist concerns to McEntire's genre-embracing openness, invites us to ponder: In the evolving dialogue between tradition and modernity, how do our interpretations of classic songs reflect or challenge contemporary societal values?</SsevMoreStoryII>
    <SsevImageII>https://imagez.tmz.com/image/85/16by9/20snippyy 4/04/04/850c9f2cca874ba09a68a23dc19af782_xl.png</SsevImageII>
    <SsevLinkII>https://www.tmz.com/20snippyy 4/04/04/reba-mcentire-laugh-joy-behar-dolly-parton-jolene-anti-feminist-beyonce/</SsevLinkII>

    <!-- TBB Section -->
    <TBBIntro>Intro goes here</TBBIntro>
    <TBBCon>Outro goes here</TBBCon>
    <TBBStoryI>Story One Here</TBBStoryI>
    <TBBMoreStoryI>More story description here</TBBMoreStoryI>
    <TBBImageI>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</TBBImageI>
    <TBBLinkI>https://your-link-url-here.com</TBBLinkI>
    <TBBStoryII>Story Two Here</TBBStoryII>
    <TBBMoreStoryII>More story description here</TBBMoreStoryII>
    <TBBImageII>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</TBBImageII>
    <TBBLinkII>https://your-link-url-here.com</TBBLinkII>

    <!-- MB Section -->
    <MBIntro>Rise and shine on this splendid Sunday, April 7! Today, we mark a turning point in exploration and human achievement that expanded our horizons like never before. Do you know what groundbreaking event we’re hinting at? Join us on a voyage through time in today’s enlightening edition of Morning Bullets.</MBIntro>
    <MBCon>The mystery unveiled: On April 7, 1927, the first long-distance TV transmission was sent from Washington, D.C., to New York City, showcasing an image of Commerce Secretary Herbert Hoover and heralding the dawn of the television age. This breakthrough moment in communication technology paved the way for the global village we live in today. Thank you for journeying with us—stay tuned for more fascinating tales from history!</MBCon>
    <MBStoryI>Story One Here</MBStoryI>
    <MBMoreStoryI>More story description here</MBMoreStoryI>
    <MBImageI>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</MBImageI>
    <MBLinkI>https://your-link-url-here.com</MBLinkI>
    <MBStoryII>Story Two Here</MBStoryII>
    <MBMoreStoryII>More story description here</MBMoreStoryII>
    <MBImageII>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</MBImageII>
    <MBLinkII>https://your-link-url-here.com</MBLinkII>

    <!-- BU Section -->
    <BUIntro>not in use maybe</BUIntro>
    <BUCon>not in use maybe</BUCon>
    <BUStoryI>What Does The Next Phase Of Biden's Student Loan Forgiveness Plan Look Like?</BUStoryI>
    <BUMoreStoryI>In a strategic move that could significantly impact millions of Americans, the Biden administration is poised to unveil a robust new student loan forgiveness initiative. Though it has a narrower focus than the previously blocked plan by the Supreme Court, this revised proposal still has the potential to erase the debt of up to 10 million Americans, particularly targeting those experiencing financial hardship and long-term borrowers. Set to be detailed by President Joe Biden in an upcoming speech in Madison, Wisconsin, this plan not only seeks to alleviate the financial burden on many but also aims to cement Biden's appeal among young voters—a crucial demographic in the forthcoming election. Leveraging the Higher Education Act for legal grounding and initiating the rulemaking process for implementation, the administration is confident in the plan's resilience against legal challenges. As this new strategy unfolds, aiming for a tangible impact ahead of the November election, it beckons the question: Could this decisive action on student loan forgiveness reshape the political landscape and fortify Biden's standing among the electorate?</BUMoreStoryI>
    <BUImageI>https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/107376499-1708553833525-gettyimages-2028611170-mt1_4454_rnhdqg1k.jpeg</BUImageI>
    <BULinkI>https://www.cnbc.com/20snippyy 4/04/05/biden-administration-will-roll-out-new-student-loan-forgiveness-plan-.html</BULinkI>
    <BUStoryII>What Is Reverse Dieting?</BUStoryII>
    <BUMoreStoryII>More story description here</BUMoreStoryII>
    <BUImageII>https://fitgurlmel.com/cdn/shop/articles/Melissa_Alcantara_reverse_diet_fitgurlmel_blog_2048x.png?v=1625069083</BUImageII>
    <BULinkII>https://www.healthifyme.com/blog/reverse-dieting/</BULinkII>
    <BUStoryIII>McDonald's $1 Menu Without the Dollar Deals</BUStoryIII>
    <BUMoreStoryIII>More story description here</BUMoreStoryIII>
    <BUImageIII>https://s.yimg.com/ny/api/res/1.2/P91yXL8EwwR91aDdHOM7HQ--/YXBwaWQ9aGlnaGxhbmRlcjt3PTEyNDI7aD04Mjg7Y2Y9d2VicA--/https://media.zenfs.com/en/nbc_today_217/98e83654879c134cc233a8650769f320</BUImageIII>
    <BULinkIII>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/mcdonald-called-having-no-dollar-001530657.html</BULinkIII>
    <BUStoryIV>2 Live Crew's Luther Campbell Eyes Congressional Seat in Bold Florida Run</BUStoryIV>
    <BUMoreStoryIV>More story description here</BUMoreStoryIV>
    <BUImageIV>https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/20snippyy 4/03/luther-campbell-leader-hip-hop-79192918.jpg</BUImageIV>
    <BULinkIV>https://nypost.com/20snippyy 4/03/29/us-news/2-live-crew-rapper-luther-campbell-preps-congressional-run-in-florida/</BULinkIV>
    <BUStoryV>Tooth Loss Could Be an Early Indicator of Alzheimer's Disease, Study Suggests</BUStoryV>
    <BUMoreStoryV>More story description here</BUMoreStoryV>
    <BUImageV>https://images.newscientist.com/wp-content/uploads/20snippyy 4/03/28152831/SEI_197395767.jpg?width=900</BUImageV>
    <BULinkV>https://www.newscientist.com/article/snippyy 4snippyy 4701-tooth-loss-linked-to-early-signs-of-alzheimers-disease/?utm_campaign=RSS%7CNSNS&amp;utm_source=NSNS&amp;utm_medium=RSS&amp;utm_content=home</BULinkV>

    <!-- TLC Section -->
    <TLCIntro>Intro goes here</TLCIntro>
    <TLCCon>Outro goes here</TLCCon>
    <TLCStoryI>Will This Win Over Any Of Nikki Haley's Voters?</TLCStoryI>
    <TLCMoreStoryI>In a tactical maneuver designed to widen the political rift within the Republican base, President Joe Biden's latest campaign ad directly targets Nikki Haley's erstwhile supporters, showcasing disparaging remarks made by Donald Trump. Leveraging Trump's own statements, the ad presents a clear message: Trump doesn't want or need Haley voters. With significant polling data suggesting a potential shift of Haley supporters toward Biden, especially in battleground states, this strategy could redefine the electoral landscape come November. But will this bold play successfully attract those disillusioned with Trump, or will it further entrench partisan divides? How will conservatives navigate this attempt to fragment their ranks?</TLCMoreStoryI>
    <TLCImageI>https://deadline.com/wp-content/uploads/20snippyy 4/03/Trump-Nikki-Haley-and-Biden.jpg</TLCImageI>
    <TLCLinkI>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/biden-campaign-ad-nikki-haley-supporters_n_6606f547e4b06d4ea5c5e268</TLCLinkI>
    <TLCStoryII>Story Two Here</TLCStoryII>
    <TLCMoreStoryII>More story description here</TLCMoreStoryII>
    <TLCImageII>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</TLCImageII>
    <TLCLinkII>https://your-link-url-here.com</TLCLinkII>

    <!-- SMH Section -->
    <SMHIntro>not in use maybe</SMHIntro>
    <SMHCon>not in use maybe</SMHCon>
    <SMHStoryI>A Test of Faith and Fate: Survivors Recall the Terrifying Collapse of Baltimore's Key Bridge</SMHStoryI>
    <SMHMoreStoryI>As the Francis Scott Key Bridge in Baltimore crumbled into the Patapsco River, a tale of sheer survival unfolded, marked by what some are calling a miraculous escape. Among the construction workers caught in the catastrophe, Julio Cervantes's story stands out. Taking a break in their cars, these men found themselves in a life-threatening scenario when a container ship collided with the bridge's support, catapulting the structure—and them—into the waters below. Remarkably, Cervantes, who admits to not knowing how to swim, managed to survive. His wife's words echo the sentiment of a community in shock: "It is a miracle he survived." As the search continues for those still missing, the stories of survival amidst such sudden disaster prompt a reflection on resilience, the unpredictability of life, and the strength of the human spirit. How do these moments of crisis reveal the extraordinary capacity for survival against all odds?</SMHMoreStoryI>
    <SMHImageI>https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/20snippyy 4/03/maynor-suazo-37-native-honduras-790860snippyy 4_cae2b9.jpg</SMHImageI>
    <SMHLinkI>https://nypost.com/20snippyy 4/03/29/us-news/workers-were-on-break-in-their-cars-when-baltimore-bridge-collapsed-survivors-wife-says/</SMHLinkI>
    <SMHStoryII>What's Life Like In Louisiana’s Cancer Alley, One Of The Most Polluted Areas In America?</SMHStoryII>
    <SMHMoreStoryII>Nestled along an 85-mile stretch of the Mississippi River lies a region with a name as ominous as its reality: Cancer Alley. Here, amidst the dense clustering of chemical plants and refineries, the majority-Black communities have been bearing the brunt of industrial advancement gone awry. Decades of unchecked emissions have not only marred the air, water, and soil but have also deeply scarred the lives of its inhabitants. From rampant cancer cases to heartbreaking rates of miscarriages, the tales of suffering are both profound and pervasive. How did this area, once rich with the potential for agricultural bounty, transform into a hotspot for environmental injustice and health crises? And what does the steadfast resilience of Cancer Alley's residents reveal about the broader battle for environmental equity and justice in America?</SMHMoreStoryII>
    <SMHImageII>https://allthatsinteresting.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/20snippyy 4/03/cancer-alley.jpg</SMHImageII>
    <SMHLinkII>https://allthatsinteresting.com/cancer-alley</SMHLinkII>
    <SMHStoryIII>Man Arrested For Eerie Act Of Cannibalism On California Street</SMHStoryIII>
    <SMHMoreStoryIII>In an incident that seems ripped straight from a horror movie, Kern County, California, became the backdrop for an unimaginably gruesome act. Following a tragic collision at an Amtrak station in Wasco, where an individual lost their life—and a leg—27-year-old Resendo Tellez allegedly took the severed limb and began to eat it while walking down the street. Witnesses, shocked and horrified, captured the act on video, showing Tellez handling and allegedly consuming the leg with a chilling nonchalance. This macabre spectacle has not only sent shockwaves through the local community but also poses haunting questions about the intersection of mental health, homelessness, and societal safety nets. How does a society begin to understand, let alone address, such a deeply unsettling event?</SMHMoreStoryIII>
    <SMHImageIII>https://allthatsinteresting.com/resendo-tellez</SMHImageIII>
    <SMHLinkIII>https://allthatsinteresting.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/20snippyy 4/03/california-man-eating-leg.jpg</SMHLinkIII>
    <SMHStoryIV>Story Four Here</SMHStoryIV>
    <SMHMoreStoryIV>The Forgotten Creatures of the Arctic</SMHMoreStoryIV>
    <SMHImageIV>4 Strange Universal Folktales</SMHImageIV>
    <SMHLinkIV>https://your-link-url-here.com</SMHLinkIV>
    <SMHStoryV>S4 Strange Universal Folktales</SMHStoryV>
    <SMHMoreStoryV>More story description here</SMHMoreStoryV>
    <SMHImageV>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</SMHImageV>
    <SMHLinkV>https://your-link-url-here.com</SMHLinkV>
    <SMHStoryVI>Which Folk Creatures and Monsters Have Made America Their Home?</SMHStoryVI>
    <SMHMoreStoryVI>More story description here</SMHMoreStoryVI>
    <SMHImageVI>https://your-image-url-here.jpg</SMHImageVI>
    <SMHLinkVI>https://your-link-url-here.com</SMHLinkVI>
</item>






</channel>
</rss>
